<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Skinny Comps</string>

    <string name="header_daily_habits">Fill out the Daily Life Chart each day to  track your wellness habits!</string>
    <string name="bot_text">Fill out the Daily Life Chart each day to  track your wellness habits!</string>
    <string name="qwerty">theskinnyconfidential</string>
    <string name="qwerty2">KIMKELLYFIT</string>
    <string name="daily_habits_header">Fill out the Daily Life Chart each day to track your wellness habits!</string>
    <string name="download_your_daily_habits_chart">DOWNLOAD YOUR DAILY HABITS CHART</string>
    <string name="breakfast_daily_habits">Breakfast</string>
    <string name="text_daily_habits_1"><![CDATA[KIM & LAURYN NEVER SKIP BREAKFAST. Two & half hours later is always a snack. They both love fiber, protein, greens, & LIGHT, healthy fat. Make sure you\'re eating enough to rev up your metabolism. When you go long stretches of time without food, you\'re slowing down your metabolism. You don\'t want to train your body to store fat. SO eat. Especially breakfast. It sets the tone of the day.]]></string>
    <string name="self_care">Self-Care</string>
    <string name="text_daily_habits_2"><![CDATA[Lauryn & Kim LOVE SELF-CARE. This can be anything from meditation, chiropractor, acupuncture, cupping, massage, facials, hot bath, aromatherapy, rosé (HAHA), listening podcasts, reading, etc. When you\'re your best self, you can show up for other\'s better. Self-care is SO IMPORTANT.]]></string>
    <string name="text_daily_habits_3"><![CDATA[Lauryn likes to aim for 7 to 9 and Kim likes to get 7 to 8 hours. Sleep is SO IMPORTANT. Get in bed & unplug at least an hour before. Lauryn likes to read a hard-cover book before bed & Kim likes to listen to music or meditate. They both like noise-canceling headphones too (so Lauryn can avoid Michael\'s 384732 questions).]]></string>
    <string name="water">Water</string>
    <string name="text_dayly_habits_4"><![CDATA[We know, we know- this is what everyone tells you BUT it\'s important. Aim for half your body weight in ounces. Kim & Lauryn carry around a Hydroflask (Lauryn especially loves her pink Starbucks cup). Both of them keep the water cold which is ideal. Get creative with your water- use non-caffeinated tea, add mint, lemon, berries, or basil (Lauryn loves basil in her water, Kim loves basil & strawberries in her water). Even freezing berries in ice & adding them to your water feels special. If you\'re not into water, set alarms in your phone to remind you to GULPY-GULP. If you\'re drinking, have a glass of water for every cocktail! ALWAYS. Try for non-bubbly if you\'re drinking alcohol. Lauryn LOVES PEPPERMINT TEA. Lately she\'s been doing mint leaves in hot water. This soothes the digestive system. Kim loves a straw because it\'s easier to drink. The Hydroflask has a straw built in & Lauryn loves SoftyStraws too. Water-based foods like cucumber, lettuce, & watermelon are great too.]]></string>
    <string name="sex">Sex</string>
    <string name="text_daily_habits_5">Sex is a mood-lifting hormone! Get in sex when you can- HA. It\'s your feel good hormone. If you can\'t have sex, 2018 is all about the self-love. Have some fun. We both love coconut oil based lube like WOO FOR PLAY.</string>
    <string name="steps">Steps</string>
    <string name="text_daily_habits_6">Lauryn likes to count her steps on the PACER APP. Kim likes her Apple watch. Both are great. They both like to aim for 10k minimum a day, but 15k is a goal (very ideal!). Lauryn likes to get her steps in on the Treadmill while returning e-mails. Kim likes to park far away from where she has to go. Kim also likes to walk her dog while on a conference call. Be resourceful!</string>
    <string name="sweat">Sweat</string>
    <string name="text_daily_habits_7">This is obvious. TRY TO BREAK A SWEAT ONCE A DAY. 7 minute workouts count!</string>
    <string name="text_daily_habits_8">Fill out the Daily Life Chart each day to track your wellness habits!</string>
    <string name="text_button_daily_habits_2">DOWNLOAD YOUR DAILY HABITS CHART</string>
    <string name="_15_best_plant_based_protein_sources">15 BEST PLANT-BASED PROTEIN SOURCES</string>
    <string name="green_peace">GREEN PEACE</string>
    <string name="quinoa">QUINOA</string>
    <string name="nuts_and_betters">NUTS AND BETTERS</string>
    <string name="beans">BEANS</string>
    <string name="checkpeas">CHECKPEAS</string>
    <string name="tempeh_and_tofu">TEMPEH AND TOFU</string>
    <string name="edamame">EDAMAME</string>
    <string name="leafy_greens">LEAFY GREENS</string>
    <string name="hemp">HEMP</string>
    <string name="chia_seeds">CHIA SEEDS</string>
    <string name="sesamr_sunflower_and_poppy_seeds">SESAMR, SUNFLOWER, AND POPPY SEEDS</string>
    <string name="seitan">SEITAN</string>
    <string name="non_dairy_milk">NON-DAIRY MILK</string>
    <string name="unsweetened_cocoa_powder">UNSWEETENED COCOA POWDER</string>
    <string name="avoid">Avoid</string>
    <string name="soy_full_of_gos_linked_to_disease">+ soy - full of GOs linked to disease</string>
    <string name="dairy_if_vegan">+ dairy,if vegan</string>
    <string name="addivives_and_processed_ingredients">+ addivives and processed ingredients</string>
    <string name="whey_that_is_pasteurized_and_heat_ntreated_disruptive_to_health">+ whey that is pasteurized and heat  treated - disruptive to health</string>
    <string name="look_for">Look for</string>
    <string name="building_muscle_whey_amp_whey_isolates_bcaas"><![CDATA[+ building muscle = whey & whey isolates, BCAAs]]></string>
    <string name="lose_weight_no_added_sugars_or_maldextrons_no_bcaas">+ lose weight = no added sugars or maldextrons, no BCAAs</string>
    <string name="vegan_use_plant_proteins_such_as_hemp_or_pea">+ vegan - use plant proteins such as hemp or pea</string>
    <string name="a_brand_that_tests_for_level_of_poisons">+ a brand that tests for level of poisons</string>
    <string name="how_amp_why"><![CDATA[How & Why]]></string>
    <string name="post_workout_consume_protein_within_30_minutes">+ post workout = consume protein within 30 minutes</string>
    <string name="muscles_are_most_responsive_for_growth_and_repair_during_that_time">+ muscles are most responsive for growth and repair during that time.</string>
    <string name="protein_keeps_body_filled_longer_and_doesn_t_turn_to_fat">+ protein keeps body filled longer and doesn’t turn to fat.</string>
    <string name="spread_out_throughout_the_day_your_body_breaks_down_25_g_per_meal">+ spread out throughout the day - your body breaks down 25 g per meal</string>
    <string name="example">Example:</string>
    <string name="if_you_re_beginning_to_workout_amp_weigh_125_lbs_60_g_protein_day"><![CDATA[If you’re beginning to workout & weigh 125 lbs (~60 g protein / day)]]></string>
    <string name="green_smoothie_20_g">+ Green smoothie ( 20 g )</string>
    <string name="turkey_salad_lunch_25_g">+ Turkey salad lunch ( 25 g )</string>
    <string name="chicken_breast_dinner_20_g">+ Chicken breast dinner ( 20 g )</string>
    <string name="positive_talk">Positive Talk</string>
    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="tips_text_1">YES — talking positively to yourself. Celebrate your victories — tiny ones AND large ones. \"I feel great! This is going to be awesome! I can’t wait to feel and look even more amazing! I got this!\" Keep pushing and FINISH! The way we talk to ourselves matters. MAKE IT ALL INSANELY POSITIVE. Remember your thoughts become your actions!</string>
    <string name="tips_text_2">Schedule your workout like an appointment! Is it going to be first thing in the morning, during your lunch hour, when your kids are napping, after work? When? Put it in your phone, and DO NOT COMPROMISE!!! You don\'t miss your hair, nails or lash appointment, so you CERTAINLY are not going to miss your GET FIT appointment.</string>
    <string name="consistency">Consistency</string>
    <string name="tips_text_3">Results come from work. True work! This means consistently putting in the effort when working and doing. Honor yourself and your health enough to make it a priority in your everyday life. Stick with the program and you\'ll see results.</string>
    <string name="commitment">Commitment</string>
    <string name="tips_text_4"><![CDATA[What is your WHY? Why are you committing to this program. What do you want from it? Where are you going? There’s got to be something in you that WANTS a change. Some kind of change. It doesn’t have to be physique — wise. Write it down & put it on your mirror. Maybe even make a vision board. VISUALIZE and COMMIT!]]></string>
    <string name="preparation">Preparation</string>
    <string name="tips_text_5">Have everything ready to go! Try laying out your workout clothes the night before or even sleeping in them for those early mornings. Pack your gym bag and place it by the door. You can even text a friend to see if she can join. Give her the exact time and location. Go REGARDLESS of who else is joining!</string>
    <string name="effort">Effort</string>
    <string name="tips_text_6">OK — this may seem harsh, but you need to get a bit uncomfortable and learn to PUSH yourself! Know good pain vs. bad pain and accept it. Remember that famous quote, “Your mind will quit a thousand times before you body will. Feel the fear and do it anyway.”</string>
    <string name="openness">Openness</string>
    <string name="realistic">Realistic</string>
    <string name="tips_text_7">There will be MANY obstacles — get ready to hurdle them. Some days you may be exhausted, not feeling so great, upset, sad, anxious... guess what? Skipping the workout or eating a bunch of cookies won’t make those feelings better, most likely it will make them worse.</string>
    <string name="tips_text_8"><![CDATA[Be realistic about your time frame when looking for results. If you are consistently prepared, put in the time and effort, open-minded & committed to this program, it will work. We like to call it “stick and stay.”]]></string>
    <string name="go_to_the_community_now">GO TO THE COMMUNITY NOW</string>
    <string name="private_facebook_tsc_body_group">PRIVATE FACEBOOK TSC BODY GROUP</string>
    <string name="community_text_1">Kim and Lauryn will be checking in to touch base with everyone and to help you stay motivated!We are all in this together. Although these workouts will most likely be done solo in your home, backyard, garage or park, we want to hear from you!</string>
    <string name="connect_with_us_here">CONNECT WITH US HERE</string>
    <string name="how_to_join">HOW TO JOIN:</string>
    <string name="community_text_2">open Facebook and search: The Skinny Confidential Body. click “JOIN.” Answer the question (what’s your e-mail) and we will match your e-mail with your order number.</string>
    <string name="members_only">MEMBERS ONLY</string>
    <string name="access_now">ACCESS NOW</string>
    <string name="www_theskinnyconfidential_com">WWW.THESKINNYCONFIDENTIAL.COM</string>
    <string name="the_skinny_confidential_on_social_media">THE SKINNY CONFIDENTIAL ON SOCIAL MEDIA</string>
    <string name="plus_giveaways">+ plus GIVEAWAYS</string>
    <string name="quick_snacks_of_the_day">+ QUICK snacks of the day</string>
    <string name="our_latest_grocery_store_finds">+ our LATEST grocery store finds</string>
    <string name="new_recipes">+ NEW recipes</string>
    <string name="much_more">+ much more!</string>
    <string name="you_will_receive">YOU WILL RECEIVE:</string>
    <string name="bonus_workouts_think_arm_toner_ab_blaster_booty_call_tighter_thighs">+ BONUS workouts. Think Arm Toner, Ab blaster, Booty Call, Tighter Thighs</string>
    <string name="www_kimkellyfit_com">WWW.KIMKELLYFIT.COM</string>
    <string name="kim_kelly_fit_on_social_media">KIM KELLY FIT ON SOCIAL MEDIA</string>
    <string name="how_to_use_it">HOW TO USE IT:</string>
    <string name="post_pictures_after_you_ve_completed_your_workout">+ post pictures after you\'ve completed your workout</string>
    <string name="share_your_progress_and_struggles">+ share your progress and struggles</string>
    <string name="show_us_what_protein_you_re_eating_post_workout">+ show us what protein you\'re eating post workout</string>
    <string name="encourage_others_and_find_support_to_quot_get_it_done_quot">+ encourage others and find support to \"get it done\"</string>
    <string name="let_s_sweet">LET\'S SWEET</string>
    <string name="prepare_text_1"><![CDATA[Your workouts can be invigorating, fun, challenging and rewarding in short amounts of time. Many of you have watched Lauryn’s Instagram & Snapchat stories regarding her weekly workouts. \nKim has been training Lauryn for over a year now, and they both understand and relate to BUSY LIVES! We wanted to be able to share these creative, effective workouts with the entire community. NOW, you can do them with her. LET’S DO THIS!]]></string>
    <string name="prepare_text_3"><![CDATA[DAY ONE we will focus on Legs & Ass  DAY TWO we will focus on Arms & Back  DAY THREE we will do Full Shebang  *don’t fret — every workout includes ABS + CARDIO.]]></string>
    <string name="prepare_text_4">We have also included TWO BONUS MINUTES for every workout. You will have a ONE MINUTE CARDIO burst choice and a ONE MINUTE PLANK VARIATION choice.</string>
    <string name="prepare_text_5"><![CDATA[These workouts will be 28 minutes in total. You do Circuit One 2X at 7 min each and Circuit Two 2X at 7 min each. THEN, if you take the Cardio & Core challenge it will equal 30 MINUTES.]]></string>
    <string name="prepare_text_6">If you are tight on time on a particular day, we encourage you NOT TO SKIP your workout! You could always do one round of each circuit, which of course would total 14 minutes. We bet you can find at least 14 minutes in your busy day.</string>
    <string name="start_workout">START WORKOUT</string>
    <string name="prepare_text_7">WHAT DO I DO ON DAYS I\'M NOT DOING TSC WORKOUT?</string>
    <string name="track_your_progress">TRACK YOUR PROGRESS</string>
    <string name="how_amp_when_to_take_photos_amp_measurements"><![CDATA[HOW & WHEN TO TAKE PHOTOS & MEASUREMENTS]]></string>
    <string name="prepare_text_8"><![CDATA[Lauryn & Kim recommend taking your photos every 2 weeks. This will help you track your gradual progression.]]></string>
    <string name="when_taking_photos">WHEN TAKING PHOTOS</string>
    <string name="_1_same_setting_each_time_and_similar_lighting">1. Same setting each time and similar lighting</string>
    <string name="_2_same_clothing_either_bikini_or_jog_bra_and_shorts">2. Same clothing (either bikini or jog bra and shorts)</string>
    <string name="prepare_text_9"><![CDATA[3. Chin up, chest up & let hands naturally fall to your sides]]></string>
    <string name="_4_full_length_body_shot">4. Full length body shot</string>
    <string name="_5_shoot_front_side_and_back_if_possible">5. Shoot front, side and back (if possible)</string>
    <string name="when_taking_measurements">WHEN TAKING MEASUREMENTS</string>
    <string name="use_a_loose_measuring_tape">*Use a loose measuring tape.</string>
    <string name="_1_wear_either_super_tight_fitted_tank_and_leggings_or_bra_and_underwear_bathing_suit_or_nothing_at_all">1. Wear either super tight fitted tank and leggings or bra and underwear, bathing suit or nothing at all!</string>
    <string name="_2_stand_with_feet_together_chin_up_chest_up">2. Stand with feet together, chin up, chest up</string>
    <string name="chest">CHEST</string>
    <string name="prepare_text_10">Wrap the tape around biggest part of the chest (right at center nipple).</string>
    <string name="waist">WAIST</string>
    <string name="prepare_text_11">Wrap the tape around mid-waist so it wraps over belly button.</string>
    <string name="hips">HIPS</string>
    <string name="prepare_text_12">Wrap the tape around the hips so it wraps around center of the buttocks.</string>
    <string name="thighs">THIGHS</string>
    <string name="prepare_text_13">You can do just one side. Separate legs apart, let your hands fall naturally at your sides, stand tall. Measure the circumference of your thigh wherever your thumb is naturally hitting your leg</string>
    <string name="increase_the_burn">INCREASE THE BURN</string>
    <string name="well_here_are_some_tips_to_bump_up_your_burn">Well, here are some tips to BUMP UP YOUR BURN:</string>
    <string name="prepare_text_14">Want to make your workout more challenging, or maybe you\'re in week 3 or 4, feeling darn good and you\'re ready for more?</string>
    <string name="plank_holds_try_lifting_one_leg_off_ground_half_the_time_then_switch_sides">+ plank holds — try lifting one leg off ground half the time then switch sides.</string>
    <string name="lunges_90_degree_angle_lunge_on_every_rep">+ LUNGES — 90 degree angle lunge on every rep.</string>
    <string name="squats_90_degree_bend_in_knee_or_even_lower_if_knees_permit">+ SQUATS —90 degree bend in knee or even lower if knees permit.</string>
    <string name="take_less_breaks_in_between_sets_continuous_movement">+ TAKE LESS BREAKS in between sets — CONTINUOUS MOVEMENT!</string>
    <string name="gauge_your_intensity_by_the_ability_to_answer_a_question_most_of_this_workout_you_should_be_able_to_answer_with_1_word_max_keep_it_intense">+ gauge your intensity by the ability to answer a question. MOST of this workout you should be able to answer with 1 word MAX! KEEP IT INTENSE!</string>
    <string name="airplane_mode_for_phone_only_use_technology_for_timing_the_workout_take_pics_and_send_to_lauryn_amp_kim_after_you_ve_finished"><![CDATA[+ airplane mode for phone. only use technology for timing the workout. take pics and send to Lauryn & Kim AFTER you\'ve finished.]]></string>
    <string name="straighten_your_legs_during_tricep_dips">+ straighten your legs during tricep dips.</string>
    <string name="if_you_re_nailing_all_exercises_in_time_frame_easily_then_increase_the_rep_count">+ if you\'re nailing all exercises in time frame easily, then increase the rep count.</string>
    <string name="for_plyometrics_push_off_the_ground_with_more_intensity_go_higher_and_land_lower_in_your_position">+ for plyometrics: push off the ground with more intensity (go higher) and land lower in your position.</string>
    <string name="go_all_the_way_to_the_ground_with_your_chest_during_any_push_up_variation">+ go ALL THE WAY to the ground with your chest during any push up variation.</string>
    <string name="come_off_your_knees_during_any_push_up_variation">+ come off your knees during any push up variation.</string>
    <string name="add_a_push_up_to_any_type_of_burpee">+ add a push up to any type of burpee.</string>
    <string name="add_a_versa_loop_band_over_wrists_during_step_ups_knee_ups_jacknives_any_situation_where_you_don_t_have_weights_in_your_hands">+ add a Versa Loop band over wrists during step ups, knee ups, jacknives (any situation where you don\'t have weights in your hands).</string>
    <string name="add_a_versa_loop_band_on_the_thighs_to_any_squat_type_of_exercise">+ add a Versa Loop band on the thighs to any squat type of exercise.</string>
    <string name="adding_weights_to_basically_any_exercise_will_increase_the_intensity">+ adding weights to basically any exercise will increase the intensity.</string>
    <string name="if_weather_permits_outdoor_activities_of_any_sort_tennis_volleyball_beach_games_dog_walking_hiking_cycling_swimming">If weather permits, outdoor activities of any sort – tennis, volleyball, beach games, dog walking, hiking, cycling, swimming.</string>
    <string name="get_outside">GET OUTSIDE!</string>
    <string name="text_12ewds">Stretch! We have provided several stretching options in this guide. Please take 10 minutes 4-6 times per week and choose 4-6 of these stretches (pg. 66). Hold each for minimum of 30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="stretch">STRETCH!</string>
    <string name="yoga">YOGA!</string>
    <string name="a_nice_relaxing_restorative_class_can_be_great_for_the_mind_as_well_as_the_body">A nice, relaxing, restorative class can be great for the mind as well as the body.</string>
    <string name="text_132efwsad">Yes it matters! Walking, hiking, jogging and running - it all matters! Kim uses her Apple Watch and Lauryn uses her phone.</string>
    <string name="steps1">STEPS!</string>
    <string name="meditation">MEDITATION!</string>
    <string name="aim_for_3_5_times_per_week_some_do_it_daily_right_on">Aim for 3-5 times per week. Some do it daily - right on!</string>
    <string name="shop_ingredients">SHOP INGREDIENTS</string>
    <string name="skip_timer_start_workout">Skip timer start workout</string>
    <string name="hello_hi_what_s_up">HELLO, HI, WHAT\'S UP ?!</string>
    <string name="you_are_here_because_you_re_creating_your_own_healthy_future">YOU ARE HERE BECAUSE YOU\'RE CREATING YOUR OWN HEALTHY FUTURE.</string>
    <string name="text_big_about"><![CDATA[But really, that\'s what it is: YOU OWNING YOUR LIFE & GOING AFTER IT. This guide is designed for the girl who wants to be the best version of themselves- someone who wants to be efficient but still has to go. What do I mean by GO? I mean you have to go- you\'re busy. It needs to be a quickie. We can\'t be cooking up a salmon every day over grilled, restaurant-worthy veggies. Time is money! Let\'s go, right? Sometimes the hustle & bustle can be overwhelming- trust me, I get it. Really though, this guide was designed for someone who has a similar lifestyle to me- someone who is slammed on time & wants something laid out in the most effective way possible. I GOT YOU. Well not just me - my trainer, KIM KELLY, too. Which is great because we love a RESOURCE! It\'s for the babe on the go, the girl who\'s late, the mom who\'s tired- no matter where you\'re starting from we have steps to get you to where you want to be. We’re talking FILLING, QUICK, SIMPLE, DELICIOUS recipes that will go with you from home, to the office, to date night. LOTS of skinny hacks. Supplement tips. Portion control talk. Workouts- but like ones you can do while watching Real Housewives. Again- everything is to the point. We don\'t screw around. Especially when it comes to your time.]]></string>
    <string name="text_about_3"><![CDATA[OH & YES, you can have alcohol & sweets while still reaching for the stars.]]></string>
    <string name="yessss_you_can_have_it_all">YESSSS, YOU CAN HAVE IT ALL.</string>
    <string name="ok_let_s_do_this_it_s_kale_champagne_squat_time"><![CDATA[Ok, let\'s do this. It\'s kale, champagne, & squat time.]]></string>
    <string name="x_lauryn_amp_kim_let_s_sweat"><![CDATA[x, lauryn & kim LET’S SWEAT]]></string>
    <string name="meet_your_workout_partner">Meet your workout partner:</string>
    <string name="lauryn_evarts_bosstick">LAURYN EVARTS BOSSTICK</string>
    <string name="text_about_4"><![CDATA[Lauryn Evarts Bosstick is the creator of the blog, book and podcast The Skinny Confidential. It represents the movers, the shakers, and the ones who, without a doubt, want to be the best damn version of themselves. The Skinny Confidential is about living your best life with kale in one hand and champagne in the other. The Skinny Confidential has been featured in SHAPE, Women’s Health Magazine, The Huffington Post, SELF Magazine, & Who What Wear. She lives in Southern California with her husband, Michael & their two chihuahuas, Pixy and T. Boone Pickens. Lauryn created this guide to showcase all of her skinny tips and tricks.]]></string>
    <string name="meet_your_trainer">Meet your trainer:</string>
    <string name="kim_kelly">KIM KELLY</string>
    <string name="text_about_kim"><![CDATA[Kim Kelly is a lifestyle & fitness expert in San Diego. Drawing from her experience in an array of diverse training disciplines, Kim has developed a unique and powerful fitness regimen that focuses on high intensity interval training (HIIT). At the heart of her workouts are a creative and systematic series of cardio, strength and abdominal exercises designed to achieve full body results in a short time frame. Kim’s greatest joy not only comes from seeing her clients achieve their fitness and health goals but also watching their self confidence grow as a result. Her belief that positive energy has both physical and emotional benefits is at the core of her mission to INSPIRE & MOTIVATE PEOPLE…while keeping it FUN.]]></string>
    <string name="prepare_text_2"><![CDATA[You will have the option to pick the level you would like to start with Beginner, Intermediate or Advanced. Each level will have 3 days of workouts a week. There will be 2 circuits in EACH workout and each circuit will be done twice, equaling to 4 circuits total. Circuit 1 & 3 contains 6 workouts and Circuit 2 & 4 contains 6 workouts, plus 1 plank and 1 cardio workout. All workouts are 1 minute each with an optional 10 second break between each workout, TRY NOT TO STOP for breaks during each circuit. You have an optional 30 to 60 second rest before starting the next circuit. DAY ONE we will focus on Legs & Ass DAY TWO we will focus on Arms & Back DAY THREE we will do Full Shebang These workouts will be 28 minutes in total. Circuit 1 & 3 are 6 minutes each and Circuit 2 & 4 are 8 minutes each. If you are tight on time on a particular day, we encourage you NOT TO SKIP your workout! You could always do one round of each circuit, which of course would total 14 minutes. We bet you can find at least 14 minutes in your busy day.]]></string>
    <string name="skinny_top_title"><![CDATA[Here are some basic tips. These apply to this guide & for everyday life.]]></string>
    <string name="nutrition_tips">NUTRITION TIPS</string>
    <string name="add_in">Add in:</string>
    <string name="fill_up_on_veggies">• Fill up on veggies</string>
    <string name="eat_more_fish">• Eat MORE FISH</string>
    <string name="choose_leaner_meats">• CHOOSE leaner meats</string>
    <string name="stay_hydrated_consume_half_your_bodyweight_in_ounces_of_water_everyday_more_in_warmer_climates_on_workout_days"><![CDATA[• Stay hydrated: consume HALF your bodyweight in ounces of water everyday (more in warmer climates & on workout days)]]></string>
    <string name="know_your_good_carbs">• KNOW your GOOD CARBS</string>
    <string name="crowd_out">Crowd out:</string>
    <string name="don_t_skip_breakfast">• DON’T skip breakfast</string>
    <string name="don_t_drink_all_your_meals">• DON’T DRINK ALL YOUR MEALS</string>
    <string name="protein_shakes_are_great_and_we_love_them_but_it_is_important_that_you_are_eating_real_whole_foods">• Protein shakes are great, and we love them, but it is important that you are eating real, whole foods</string>
    <string name="don_t_rely_on_protein_bars_and_packaged_foods_throughout_your_day">• DON’T RELY on protein bars and packaged foods throughout your day</string>
    <string name="limit_dairy">• LIMIT dairy</string>
    <string name="limit_white_carbs">• LIMIT white carbs</string>
    <string name="watch_hidden_sugars_and_sugar_in_general">• WATCH hidden SUGARS and sugar in general</string>
    <string name="limit_ingredients_you_can_t_pronounce">• LIMIT ingredients you can’t pronounce</string>
    <string name="limit_fried_foods">• LIMIT fried foods</string>
    <string name="choose_baked_steamed_or_grilled_foods">• CHOOSE baked, steamed or grilled foods</string>
    <string name="legumes">+ legumes</string>
    <string name="sweet_potato">+ sweet potato</string>
    <string name="whole_grains">+ whole grains</string>
    <string name="quinoa_1">+ quinoa</string>
    <string name="brown_rice">+ brown rice</string>
    <string name="food_time_when_to_eat">FOOD TIME - WHEN TO EAT</string>
    <string name="yep_skinny_hacks">Yep, it matters! - EAT BREAKFAST. This SETS your metabolism FOR THE DAY! - If you can get protein in your body within 30-40 minutes of waking, you have the ability to burn 30% MORE CALORIES that day at a resting state. - Follow the 3 meals and 2 snacks rule. TRY NOT TO GO LONGER than 3 HOURS without something in your stomach. - We DO NOT support or believe in skipping meals/snacks, because “we haven’t earned it” theory. - In fact, this will ONLY WORK AGAINST YOU! If you go long stretches of time without food, you are essentially training your body to STORE FAT and to SLOW YOUR METABOLISM DOWN. NO THANKS!</string>
    <string name="breakfast_within_40_minutes_of_waking_up_high_protein">BREAKFAST - WITHIN 40 MINUTES OF WAKING UP, HIGH PROTEIN</string>
    <string name="lunch_2_5_3_hours_later">LUNCH: 2.5-3 HOURS LATER</string>
    <string name="snack_2_5_3_hours_later">SNACK: 2.5-3 HOURS LATER</string>
    <string name="dinner_2_5_3_hours_later">DINNER: 2.5-3 HOURS LATER</string>
    <string name="light_snack_1_5_2_hours_later">LIGHT SNACK: 1.5-2 HOURS LATER</string>
    <string name="this_pattern_is_so_easy_to_maintain_if_you_are_prepared_preparation_is_key_so_we_aren_t_left_starving_and_making_poor_choices_that_s_when_we_pull_up_to_convenient_stores_and_buy_packaged_foods_or_perhaps_make_an_even_worse_decision">This pattern is SO easy to maintain if you ARE PREPARED! Preparation is key, so we aren’t left starving and making poor choices. That’s when we pull up to convenient stores and buy packaged foods or perhaps make an even worse decision.</string>
    <string name="tips">TIPS</string>
    <string name="boil_several_eggs_at_once_and_store_for_hard_boiled_egg_snacks">+ Boil several eggs at once and store for hard boiled egg snacks.</string>
    <string name="chop_up_lots_of_veggies_and_pack_them_in_containers_in_fridge">+ Chop up lots of veggies and pack them in containers in fridge.</string>
    <string name="have_salsas_hummus_mustards_etc_on_hand">+ Have salsas, hummus, mustards etc. on hand.</string>
    <string name="make_small_snack_size_bags_of_almonds">+ Make small snack size bags of almonds.</string>
    <string name="trader_joes_has_great_pre_made_salads_but_we_suggest_ditching_the_dressing_included_and_using_fresh_lemon_and_a_drizzle_of_olive_oil">+ Trader Joes has great pre-made salads, but we suggest ditching the dressing included and using fresh lemon and a drizzle of olive oil.</string>
    <string name="cook_several_chicken_breasts_at_a_time_and_cut_them_into_3_4_inch_slices_add_them_to_salads_almond_flour_tortillas_or_a_spinach_and_quinoa_bowl">+ Cook several chicken breasts at a time and cut them into 3/4 inch slices. Add them to salads, almond flour tortillas, or a spinach and quinoa bowl.</string>
    <string name="go_to_recipes">GO TO RECIPES</string>
    <string name="can_i_drink_alcohol">CAN I DRINK ALCOHOL?</string>
    <string name="ok_probably_skinny_hacks">Ok, so you are probably expecting us to say NO ALCOHOL! Well, the truth is we want this to be a REALISTIC guide; not a NO-FUN guide! With that being said, if you choose to refrain from alcohol, go for it! However, if you know you are likely going to be doing social things and may be having a drink or so throughout the week, here’s what we recommend:</string>
    <string name="limit_drinking_alcohol_to_2_3_nights_a_week">• limit drinking alcohol to 2-3 nights a week</string>
    <string name="if_you_drinking">• if you’re drinking wine, eliminate fruit or anything with “natural occurring sugars” to help your hangover</string>
    <string name="we_suggest">+ we suggest SECO wine, because they contain 0 added sugars, 0 chemicals, are non-GMO, vegan and lab tested</string>
    <string name="drink_vodka">• drink a vodka or tequila soda with fresh squeezed lemons or limes</string>
    <string name="consume_1_glass">• consume 1 glass of water for each alcoholic drink</string>
    <string name="you_ll_find_some_great_skinny_drink_recipes_in_our_food_drink_guide"><![CDATA[You’ll find some great “SKINNY” drink recipes in our food & drink guide.]]></string>
    <string name="can_i_eat_fruit">CAN I EAT FRUIT?</string>
    <string name="fruit_better">Fruit is better than a donut. So yes you can eat fruit. We suggest sticking to the following LOWER sugar fruits: Lemons, Raspberries, Strawberries, Blackberries, Kiwi, Grapefruit, Avocado (1/4 at a time/meal), Watermelon, Grapes (handful for the fiber!)</string>
    <string name="why_is_fiber_so_good_for_me_how_much_fiber_should_i_eat_per_day"><![CDATA[WHY IS FIBER SO GOOD FOR ME & HOW MUCH FIBER SHOULD I EAT PER DAY?]]></string>
    <string name="fiber_helps_you_lose_weight_while_staying_full_how">Fiber helps you lose weight while staying full! How?</string>
    <string name="fiber_is_not_digested_and_does_not_increase_blood_sugar_levels">Fiber IS NOT digested and DOES NOT increase blood sugar levels.</string>
    <string name="fiber_is_the_zero_calorie_non_digestible_part_of_a_carbohydrate">Fiber is the ZERO calorie, non-digestible part of a carbohydrate.</string>
    <string name="this_means_it_takes_your_body_a_longer_time_to_process_the_food_which_keeps_you_satisfied_longer_aka_less_hungry">This means it takes your body a longer time to process the food which keeps you satisfied longer aka less hungry!</string>
    <string name="plus_you_can_subtract_fiber_from_carbohydrate_content_when_counting_carbs_yay">PLUS, you can SUBTRACT FIBER from carbohydrate content when counting carbs – YAY!</string>
    <string name="fiber_goal_25_30_g_fiber_per_day">FIBER GOAL – 25-30 g fiber per day</string>
    <string name="substitutes">SUBSTITUTES</string>
    <string name="mushrooms_as_chips_use_them_to_dip_in_hummus_dressings_sauces">+ mushrooms as chips (use them to dip in hummus, dressings, sauces).</string>
    <string name="english_cucumber_or_jicama_as_dippers_too">+ english cucumber or jicama as dippers too.</string>
    <string name="endive_lettuce_for_chips_with_guacamole">+ endive lettuce for chips with guacamole.</string>
    <string name="hearts_of_palm_pasta_is_fab_zoodles_are_good_too">+ HEARTS OF PALM PASTA is FAB (zoodles are good too).</string>
    <string name="cauliflower_rice_cauliflower_crust_pizza_is_so_good_we_re_about_this"><![CDATA[+ cauliflower rice & cauliflower crust pizza IS SO GOOD. we\'re about this!]]></string>
    <string name="purple_cabbage_as_taco_shells">+ purple cabbage as taco shells.</string>
    <string name="cauliflower_mashed_potatoes_taste_pretty_damn_good">+ cauliflower mashed potatoes taste pretty damn good.</string>
    <string name="use_nutritional_yeast_instead_of_parmesan_cheese">+ use nutritional yeast instead of parmesan cheese.</string>
    <string name="use_coconut_aminos_instead_of_soy_we_re_not_big_soy_fans">+ use coconut aminos instead of soy- we\'re not big soy fans.</string>
    <string name="wrap_your_sushi_in_cucumber_it_s_so_good">+ wrap your sushi in cucumber. IT\'S SO GOOD.</string>
    <string name="use_gg_crackers_as_a_vehicle">+ use GG crackers as a vehicle.</string>
    <string name="order_tacos_or_burgers_wrapped_in_lettuce_instead_of_a_tortilla_or_bun">+ order tacos or burgers wrapped in lettuce instead of a tortilla or bun.</string>
    <string name="dining_out">DINING OUT</string>
    <string name="when_you_order_ask_for_no_salt">+ when you order ask for no salt.</string>
    <string name="always_modify_ask_for_veggies_instead_of_chips">+ always modify: ask for veggies instead of chips.</string>
    <string name="make_your_own_dressing_at_restaurants_olive_oil_lemon_red_wine_vinegar"><![CDATA[+ make your own dressing at restaurants: olive oil, lemon, & red wine vinegar.]]></string>
    <string name="salsa_over_ketchup">+ salsa over ketchup!</string>
    <string name="ask_for_an_oil_free_pan_ask_them_to_spray_the_pan_instead">+ ask for an oil free pan - ask them to spray the pan instead.</string>
    <string name="drink_a_full_glass_of_water_in_between_any_alcoholic_drinks">+ drink a full glass of water in between any alcoholic drinks.</string>
    <string name="habits">HABITS</string>
    <string name="bone_broth_4_x_a_week_lots_of_lemon">+ BONE BROTH 4 x a week! lots of lemon.</string>
    <string name="carry_ggs_in_your_purse_they_re_fab">+ carry GGs in your purse- they\'re fab.</string>
    <string name="protein_fiber_at_every_meal"><![CDATA[+ protein & fiber at every meal!]]></string>
    <string name="use_portion_controlled_bowls_at_home_try_not_to_eat_out_of_the_bag_try_inside_out_bowls_from_anthropologie_or_snack_sized_ziplock_bags_they_re_fab">+ use portion controlled bowls at home- try not to eat out of the bag. try INSIDE OUT BOWLS from Anthropologie or snack-sized ziplock bags. they\'re FAB.</string>
    <string name="don_t_fall_for_cocktail_mixes_make_your_own">+ don\'t fall for cocktail mixes! make your own.</string>
    <string name="don_t_fall_for_paleo_vegan_gluten_free_always_check_ingredients_we_look_at_ingredients_and_carb_counts">+ don\'t fall for paleo, vegan, gluten-free — ALWAYS check ingredients! we look at ingredients and CARB counts.</string>
    <string name="herbs_spices_are_your_friend"><![CDATA[+ HERBS & SPICES ARE YOUR FRIEND.]]></string>
    <string name="be_prepared"><![CDATA[+ be prepared: Kim loves almonds, rolled organic turkey, GGs with raw peanut butter, non-dairy yogurt with a scoop of protein & berries- get creative!]]></string>
    <string name="start_with_a_soup_or_leafy_green_salad">+ start with a soup or leafy green salad.</string>
    <string name="start_every_morning_with_lemon_water">+ start every morning with lemon water.</string>
    <string name="apple_cider_vinegar_shots_are_amazing_in_the_morning_2_3_apple_cider_vinegar_shots_are_great_throughout_the_day">+ apple cider vinegar shots are amazing in the morning! 2-3 apple cider vinegar shots are great throughout the day.</string>
    <string name="start_the_day_with_a_protein_green_smoothie_with_berries_add_spirulina"><![CDATA[+ start the day with a PROTEIN green smoothie with berries (& add spirulina!).]]></string>
    <string name="let_s_get_real_with_portions">LET’S GET REAL WITH PORTIONS</string>
    <string name="supplements_spices"><![CDATA[SUPPLEMENTS & SPICES]]></string>


</resources>
